toori michi kaeri michi
The path I take there, the path I take home
dokomademo tsudzuku you na hashi no ue
On this bridge that seems like it goes on forever
wataretara wasuretara
If I could cross over it, if I forget about it
shiranai tooi dokoka e yuketara
If I could go off towards some distant unknown place
dareka no sei da to ka dareka no tame da to ka
It’s somebody’s fault, it’s for somebody’s sake
kurikaeshi kurikaeshi kimi wa usobuite
Over and over, you shrug it off and say,
kinou wo nagesutete ashita wo akirameta you ni
Throwing yesterday away, as if you’ve given up on tomorrow
mata tojita mabuta no uragawa
I close my eyelids again, and see inside them
hyakuman shoku ni kudaketa kimi no kakera
Those pieces of you, shattered into a million colors
marude hoshi no you ni matataki wo kurikaeshita
Just like the stars above, sparkled over and over again
hyakuman shoku no monokuro ni iro aseta
They faded into a million-colored monochrome
itsuka mita yume wo
That dream I once saw
ima demo paretto ni narabete egaku
Even now, I line it up on my palette as I paint
kono utsuro de azayaka na sekai no subete
The everything of this blank and brilliant world
toori ame niwaka ame
The passing rain, the sudden rain
itsu no ma ni furihajimeta hashi no ue
When did it start falling upon this bridge?
modoretara omoidasetara
If I could go back, if I can bring myself to recall
kasa no sashikata to nanika daiji na mono
How you held out that umbrella, and something else important
sora wo aoidemita dareka omottemita
I tried to gaze up at the sky, tried to think of somebody
kurikaeshi kurikaeshi soshite utsumuite
Over and over, and then I cast my eyes down
kasuka ni nokoru you na sukoshi itami ni nita nanika
Something a bit like pain seems to have been left faintly behind
nigiritsubushita te no naka
In the palm of my clenched hand
hyakuman shoku ni kowareta kimi no kakera
Those pieces of you, broken into a million colors
marude suna no you ni yubi no sukima surinuketa
Just like fine sand, slips between my fingers
hyakuman shoku no monokuro ni irodorareta
They were colored with a million-colored monochrome
kimi ga ikiru imi
The meaning of your living
ima demo kyanbasu ni egakitsudzukeru
Even now, I continue to paint on my canvas
kono utsuro de azayaka na sekai no subete
The everything of this blank and brilliant world
hyakuman shoku ni kudaketa kimi no kakera
Those pieces of you, shattered into a million colors
marude hoshi no you ni matataki wo kurikaeshite
Just like the stars above, sparkled over and over again
hyakuman shoku no monokuro ni irodorareta
And were colored with a million-colored monochrome
hyakuman shoku ni kowareta kimi no kakera
Those pieces of you, broken into a million colors
marude hoshi no you ni oto mo naku kagayaite
Just like the stars above, glow without a sound
hyakuman shoku no monokuro ga iro ni naru
And the million-colored monochrome becomes its color
itsuka mita iro ni
That color I once saw
ima demo paretto ni narabete egaku
Even now, I line it up on my palette as I paint
kono fukanzen de kanzen na
The everything of this imperfect
sekai no subete
And perfect world