That missed chances are merely fate,
surechigai wa kekkyoku unmei de
and all just follows destiny’s plan
subete wa sujigaki toori datte
I’m not strong enough to ignore
kanashimi wo magiwaraseru hodo
the sadness of that fact
boku wa tsuyokunai kara
Every solution that’s calculated
hajikidashita kotae no subete ga
brings another one or two sacrifices
hitotsu futatsu gisei wo tomonatte
And slowly steals away my courage
mata ippou fumidasu yuuki wo
to advance another step
ubaitotte yuku
That song I once dedicated to you
itsuka kimi ni sasageta uta
is now a song of nothing but sorrowful love
ima ja kanashii dake no ai no uta
Ride on the wind and fly away,
kaze ni fukare tonde yuke
to the summer’s day when we met
bokura ga deaeta ano natsu no hi made
>start program
>function: search
>calculating...