Hurry up! isoganakucha
Hurry up! Gotta get to school on time!
tanoshii haisukuuru Day kakenukeyou
Let’s have a fun-filled sparkling high school day now
yappa ichiban Precious Memory
Always my number one precious memory
Best my place
kinou no shukudai rakushoo dattashi
Yesterday’s homework was a piece of cake
kyou wa nandaka ne
Today I feel just a bit
kibun ga wakuwaku
Excited to be here
araitateno kami nabiku
The early morning wind feels the greatest
asa ichiban ni kanjita kaze
Flowing through my just-washed hair
Happy na ichinichi wo yokan saseru wa
Making me feel like it'll be a wonderful happy day
Hurry up! isoganakucha
Hurry up! Gotta get to school on time!
tanoshii haisukuuru Day kakenukeyou
Let’s have a fun-filled sparkling high school day now
Let's go! saa tobidasou yo!
Let’s go! C’mon, take a flying leap!
tanoshii haisukuuru Day kakedasou yo
Let’s have a fun-filled dazzling high school day now
hora houkago no chaimu mo
Listen, that chime for the end of school
dokidoki tokimeki rizumikaru
Heartbeat heartthrob rhythmical
yappa ichiban Precious Memory
Always my number one precious memory
Best my place
My friends