One... two... one two three YEAH!
Just bluffing all the time
tsuyogatte bakka de nanka
Makes me feel like I'm losing, I mean, right?
son shiteru ki ga suru datte sou jan
I want to do things that shouldn't be talked about
ienai you na koto ga shitai no
Like those sorts of things
anna koto to ka
Oh gosh... what sort of things?
yada... donna koto?
Man, guys are all such idiots
otoko tte baka bakka ne
You just thought of something dirty, didn't you?
hen na koto ima kangaeta desho
You're the type that can't lie, I know
kimi tte uso ga tsukenai taipu
It's showing up pretty clearly on your face, are you ok?
daibu kao ni deteru Are you ok?
With no leeway for exceptions
joujou shakuryou no yochi nashi
It's like we can't even talk
marude ohanashi ni naranai wa
Before you go off with your grand romantic talk
soudai na roman kataru mae ni
Have you properly assessed the situation?
genjou bunseki dekiteru?
Aah! You're so dense!
aa! kimi tte donkan
Hey
nee
Come on, look this way baby
chanto kocchi muite Baby
I won't let you say No
NO nante iwasenai wa
I'm serious this time
honki moodo nan dakara
With my captivating quivering lips
omowazu mitorechau puru puru kuchibiru de
I'll make you my prisoner
kimi wo toriko ni suru no
Today's the day I'll take you on!
kyou koso shobu nan desu!