All the variables are in the first line of the script.
color1 is the primary text color
color 2 is the secondary text color
color 3 is the effects color
levels is how many layers of the text will be color2
barheight is the height of the black bars on the top and bottom
I also wrote some functions in this script
that I never used. Feel free to experiment
with them
Lunch break, I chase after
hiruyasumi hashagu koe
your laughing voice, to the library
oikakeru toshoshitsu
Your shadow flutters on the curtain
kaaten goshi yureru kage
as I peek at what you’re doing
kimi no shigusa mitsumeta
I hide my eyes from you as you read
hon wo yomu kimi ni mekakushi
Will you be angry? Will you ignore me...??
okoru kana? shikato kana...??
“You’re just like the sister I never had”!?
"hontou no imouto mitai" tte!?
What’s with that?
naze nano
Deep in my heart the sound of love
mune no oku koi no oto
beats so loudly I can hear it
takanaru hodo kikoechau yo
The truth is I’ve always been timidly
hontou wa okubyousou ni
looking towards you
itsumo kimi wo miteita
Hold on… is it still not getting through?
chotto... mada todokanai kana?