s u p e r c e l l
H E R O
That girl’s smile as she chatted
tomodachi to shabetteru
with her friends was just too lovely
sono ko no egao wa amari ni karen de
She looked just like the manga heroine of my imagination
sono sugata wa omoiegaita manga no hiroin no you da
With just one look, I fell in love
hitome mite koi ni ochita
Truly, truly in love with her
honki de honki de suki ni natta
But with a face like mine
demo ne boku no mitekure ja
I’m sure she’d hate me
kitto kirawarete shimau
There it goes again, those laughing voices
hora mata da kusu kusu warau koe
It’s fine, I’m used to this already
iin da sonna no narekko dakara
Just forget about it,
wasurete shimae
but my heart was bursting apart
dakedo mune wa harisakesou da
The young boy then meets her
shounen wa soshite deau
Wishing that none of this is just coincidence
sore wa kitto guuzen nanka janakute negatta
So that my path may cross with yours
kimi ni deaemasu you ni
I’ll wish for it a thousand times
nanmankai datte negaou
Someday, for sure!
itsuka kanarazu!
But people said that kind of miracle
keredo hito wa sonna kiseki
Couldn’t possibly be believed
shinjirareru wake nai to itta
The young girls whispered
shoujotachi ga sasayaita
“That kid’s been looking over here
"ano ko sakki kara kocchi miteru
What’s with him? It’s creepy
nan nano are kimiwarui wa
Get away, loser.”
chikadzukanaide nekura-san"
I’m sorry, I didn’t mean to…
sumimasen sonna tsumori ja…
I hung my head, but then I heard her
utsumuku boku ni kanojo no koe
“I know this guy!”
"watashi kono hito shitteru!"
Her friends are speechless, I’m stunned
mawari wa azen boku mo bouzen
“I saw those drawings on your desk
"michattan da na ano tsukue no e wo ne
Did you draw all of those?”
zenbu kimi ga kaitetari suru no?"
Ah! I’ll get laughed at again
aa! mata warawareru
But you said
dakedo kimi wa
“I like that sort of stuff.”
"aa iu no suki nan desu"
The young boy then meets her
shounen wa soshite deau
Even if thousands of millions of lightyears separate us
tatoe nanoku nanman kounen hanarete iyou ga sa
We’ll meet again for sure
zettai hikareau kara
No matter what obstacles await us there
soko ni donna shougai ga attemo
We’ll overcome them all
norikoeteku
If that can be called destiny
sore wo unmei to yobu nara
Then he would certainly be a hero
kare wa masa ni hiiroo da
But on that day I saw you
dakedo sono hi boku wa mitan da
By yourself, crying your eyes red
hitori me wo harashi naku kimi wo
How powerless I felt then
boku wa nante muryoku nan darou
But wait, what did she just say?
iiya kanojo wa nante itta?
I can’t doubt myself now
utagau na jibun no sonzai wo
The girl is waiting for someone to save her
shoujo wa sukui wo matteru
“Acting tough but crying inside
"tsuyogari de honto wa nakimushi de
That’s… almost just like me.”
etto kore tte marude watashi mitai"
She finally smiled! But as I rejoiced
yatto waratta! yorokobu boku no mae de
Her tears streamed forth
porori porori to nakidasu kanojo
What should I do!?
dou shitara ii!?
You said to me
kimi wa ittan da
“Thank you”
"arigatou" tte
The boy meets you
shounen wa kimi to deai
And finds his meaning for life
ikiru imi wo shirun da
It’s not a lie, but the truth
uso janai honto sa
And he’ll become the knight that protects you
soshite kimi wo mamoru naito ni naru
Someday, for sure
itsuka kitto ne
His left hand and her right
kare no hidarite ni wa kanojo no migite gyutto
Will grasp tightly, never to let go
nigitte hanashi wa shinai kara
And then, I meet you
soshite boku wa kimi ni deau